<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Navigation on FindSoFun - Discover Interesting AI Tools &amp; Frontend Libraries</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/navigation/</link><description>Recent content in Navigation on FindSoFun - Discover Interesting AI Tools &amp; Frontend Libraries</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/navigation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>History-in-Art: Spacetime Art Navigator</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/history-in-art-org/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/history-in-art-org/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Clicking into this site is like hopping into a time machine. Stab any country on the map, drag the timeline, and artworks from Renaissance to Modernism flash before your eyes. I tried the AI assistant by typing &amp;lsquo;Russia during the French Revolution&amp;rsquo; – it actually dug up obscure art from that era and explained the context flawlessly. Teachers would kill to use this in class; students tracing cultural relics on a map beats rote memorization any day. You might stumble upon 16th-century African sculptures conversing with Japanese ukiyo-e, suddenly seeing cultural connections click into place.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>WindowSwap: Global Window Hopping</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/window-swap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/window-swap/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is genius! Click and you&amp;rsquo;re instantly transported to someone&amp;rsquo;s window view in Italy, Japan, or anywhere really. I tried it during a stressful afternoon and found myself calming down watching rain fall through a window in Tellaro. Perfect for virtual travel inspiration, mood setting, or just escaping your own four walls. The authenticity hits different—these are real people&amp;rsquo;s real views, not curated travel footage. Feels like peeking into lives around the world with permission.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Toolify: Ultimate AI Tools Directory</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/toolify/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/toolify/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking into Toolify feels like entering an AI supermarket with 26,563 tools neatly organized. I tried the Nine Star Ki astrology AI - just input your birthdate and it generates a personalized chart with relationship insights. The most impressive part is their ranking system: monthly active users, regional popularity, revenue data&amp;hellip; you can instantly spot which tools are truly hot versus overhyped. I often browse here for creative inspiration, from video generation to pet wellness management - if it exists, it&amp;rsquo;s here. It also works as an AI industry barometer to see which sectors are taking off.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>