<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Browser Plugin on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/browser-plugin/</link><description>Recent content in Browser Plugin on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 11:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/browser-plugin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PubSpy: Lightning-Fast AdSense Lookup</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/pubspy-adsense-reverse-lookup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/pubspy-adsense-reverse-lookup/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Instant Detection
This tool specializes in AdSense reverse lookup, quickly identifying publisher IDs used by websites. It helps users discover other sites operated by the same publisher, providing a direct solution for finding all ad-monetized sites under one author.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Efficiency Boost
In practical use, simply install the Chrome extension, visit any website and click the icon to immediately get publisher information. Compared to manual queries, speed increases by 50%, with ads.txt detection reduced from 10 seconds to just 5 seconds. Bulk analysis handles hundreds of domains simultaneously, generating comprehensive reports in minutes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>User Experience
The interface is extremely clean, with non-blocking UI showing preliminary results instantly while background processing continues. The extension is only 26KB, loading in under 500ms for smooth operation. All data processing happens locally in the browser, ensuring privacy and security.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Technical Features
Dual API system guarantees 99.99% uptime, while machine learning algorithms predict publisher growth trends. Historical data spans 12 months, with interactive network mapping visualization. Export functionality supports CSV format including traffic data for further analysis.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>iGenFlow: Auto-Create Tutorials from Screen Actions</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/igenflow-automated-docs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/igenflow-automated-docs/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Automatically captures every step of web operation and generates illustrated guides in real-time. Just perform tasks normally, and it produces clear, easy-to-follow documentation without manual writing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Perfect for product documentation, customer support, and knowledge base management. Significantly improves efficiency in employee training, software reviews, and content creation, reducing manual effort by 80%.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Simple interface with one-click recording, intelligently tracks mouse clicks and keyboard inputs. Accurately identifies action areas, captures screenshots, and adds descriptions seamlessly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Install Chrome or Edge extension to start. Supports exporting to PDF, Word, and other formats. Flexible editing allows adding or deleting steps, and sharing via links enhances collaboration.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Ries.AI: Effortless English Learning Revolution</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/ries-ai-english-plugin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/ries-ai-english-plugin/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Contextual Vocabulary Integration
This browser extension intelligently blends high-frequency English words into your daily Chinese content consumption. It analyzes articles and videos in real-time, replacing select portions with English equivalents to create natural language exposure. Based on comprehensible input theory, every interaction stays within your linguistic comfort zone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Seamless Platform Integration
Works across popular platforms like Weibo, Bilibili, and Zhihu without disrupting your browsing experience. Users report significantly increased English exposure during routine internet activities, eliminating the pressure associated with traditional learning methods.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Adaptive Difficulty Adjustment
The AI dynamically calibrates replacement complexity based on your proficiency level, progressing from single words to phrases. The minimalist interface requires zero setup and activates immediately after installation. Replaced content appears in subtle highlighting that maintains reading flow while drawing appropriate attention.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Instant Setup Zero Cost
As a browser extension, installation takes one click and is completely free. All processing prioritizes local device privacy protection. It requires no change to your online habits yet delivers hundreds of daily English word exposures, enabling genuine painless progression.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>VisBug: Browser Design Powerhouse</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/visbug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/visbug/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is like a Swiss Army knife for front-end devs and designers. Open it up and it feels like a playground where every tool is right there to tinker with. I tried color adjustments—just click elements and tweak colors live, even SVG edits work seamlessly. Keyboard navigation flows like a game, Tab to traverse and Enter to select, pure efficiency. Copy-paste elements and styles across tabs? Dark mode contagion with one click? Absolutely genius. Mobile has limits but HTML5 color input still lets you have fun. No undo hurts a bit, but for free and open-source, it is ridiculously powerful. Who needs anything else?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Browserfly: AI Assistant in Your Browser</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/browserfly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/browserfly/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Picture this: an AI sidekick living right in your browser, no virtual machines or new browsers needed. Just tell it &amp;lsquo;summarize this page&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;fill out this form&amp;rsquo;, and it operates like a human would. I tried the auto-form feature – felt like having a personal assistant handling tedious tasks. You can even click any element to analyze or modify it through natural language. Imagine using it for email sorting or research automation. This isn&amp;rsquo;t another browser; it&amp;rsquo;s your existing Chrome/Edge upgraded to a smart workstation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>nTab: Idea Sparking New Tab</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/newtab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/newtab/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Every new tab feels like walking into a dev-centric bazaar: GitHub trending, Hacker News threads, and curated open-source repos laid out neatly, plus customizable bookmark zones. Tried it and instantly stopped juggling tabs for project inspiration—even my bookmark bar breathed a sigh of relief. Love how you can filter by 30+ programming languages to spot Python gems or Rust risers at a glance. Doubles as a tech radar to catch promising projects before they blow up.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>WXT: Next-gen Extension Builder</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/wxt/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/wxt/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever built browser extensions, you know the pain of configuring environments and managing builds. WXT swallows all that friction whole—built-in tools for dev, zip, and publish let you hit the ground running. I tried it: feels like Vite for extensions, with instant hot reload, native TypeScript, and auto-imports. Pick any frontend framework? No sweat. Remember struggling with MV2/MV3 compatibility? It handles it automatically. Bundling remote code? One config line. It even analyzes bundle size to keep your extension lean. Perfect for indie devs shipping side projects fast, or teams standardizing their workflow. Maybe even automate custom browser tools?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>