<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Browser Plugin on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/browser-plugin/</link><description>Recent content in Browser Plugin on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/browser-plugin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VisBug: Browser Design Powerhouse</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/visbug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/visbug/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is like a Swiss Army knife for front-end devs and designers. Open it up and it feels like a playground where every tool is right there to tinker with. I tried color adjustments—just click elements and tweak colors live, even SVG edits work seamlessly. Keyboard navigation flows like a game, Tab to traverse and Enter to select, pure efficiency. Copy-paste elements and styles across tabs? Dark mode contagion with one click? Absolutely genius. Mobile has limits but HTML5 color input still lets you have fun. No undo hurts a bit, but for free and open-source, it is ridiculously powerful. Who needs anything else?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Browserfly: AI Assistant in Your Browser</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/browserfly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/browserfly/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Picture this: an AI sidekick living right in your browser, no virtual machines or new browsers needed. Just tell it &amp;lsquo;summarize this page&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;fill out this form&amp;rsquo;, and it operates like a human would. I tried the auto-form feature – felt like having a personal assistant handling tedious tasks. You can even click any element to analyze or modify it through natural language. Imagine using it for email sorting or research automation. This isn&amp;rsquo;t another browser; it&amp;rsquo;s your existing Chrome/Edge upgraded to a smart workstation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>nTab: Idea Sparking New Tab</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/newtab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/newtab/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Every new tab feels like walking into a dev-centric bazaar: GitHub trending, Hacker News threads, and curated open-source repos laid out neatly, plus customizable bookmark zones. Tried it and instantly stopped juggling tabs for project inspiration—even my bookmark bar breathed a sigh of relief. Love how you can filter by 30+ programming languages to spot Python gems or Rust risers at a glance. Doubles as a tech radar to catch promising projects before they blow up.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>WXT: Next-gen Extension Builder</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/wxt/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/wxt/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever built browser extensions, you know the pain of configuring environments and managing builds. WXT swallows all that friction whole—built-in tools for dev, zip, and publish let you hit the ground running. I tried it: feels like Vite for extensions, with instant hot reload, native TypeScript, and auto-imports. Pick any frontend framework? No sweat. Remember struggling with MV2/MV3 compatibility? It handles it automatically. Bundling remote code? One config line. It even analyzes bundle size to keep your extension lean. Perfect for indie devs shipping side projects fast, or teams standardizing their workflow. Maybe even automate custom browser tools?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>