<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>API on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/api/</link><description>Recent content in API on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>60s API: All-in-One Open API Hub</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/docs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/docs/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is a treasure trove for developers! Open it up and it feels like walking into a data supermarket—everything&amp;rsquo;s there: daily 60-second news bites to catch up on world events, exchange rates, wallpapers, hot search rankings all at your fingertips, plus translation, IP lookup, even free Epic games. I tried the random quotes feature, and it&amp;rsquo;s like having a friend whispering fun tidbits—super engaging. Fully open-source and free, with global CDN acceleration for lightning-fast access. Imagine quickly integrating these into your projects or building a navigation site to organize these APIs, saving tons of time and effort. Got questions? Join the QQ group; the author responds fast, and the community vibe is great.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>CheckCle: Self-Hosted Monitoring Master</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/checkcle/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/checkcle/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Remember those 3AM alert calls? CheckCle is like hiring a 24/7 security guard for your servers. It does TCP, HTTPS, PING checks with surgical precision while keeping all data in your own hands. Tried the real-time analytics - feels like giving your system a full-body CT scan that instantly flags any blockage. Best part? Zero vendor lock-in. Install it and you&amp;rsquo;ve basically moved the monitoring room into your own server rack. Perfect for teams building health dashboards, plus it integrates with Discord for alerts. Finally, ops folks can sleep through the night.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Apify: Full-stack Data Extraction</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/t-a5f3e5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/t-a5f3e5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This platform is like a LEGO playground for data scraping! With 6000+ ready-to-use tools, you can grab data from TikTok to Amazon with just a few clicks. I tried the Google Maps scraper - restaurant reviews, business hours, pricing info all extracted in seconds, way faster than manual copying. The coolest part? You can build your own Actors using Python or JavaScript, feeling like assembling data robots. Imagine grabbing competitor pricing while sipping morning coffee, or automatically collecting customer feedback - now that&amp;rsquo;s efficiency!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>MCP.so: AI Tool Marketplace</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/mcp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/mcp/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Opening MCP.so feels like walking into an AI hardware store – every MCP Server is a specialized tool waiting to be plugged in. I tried the Howtocook Mcp for meal planning and it instantly killed my &amp;lsquo;what to eat&amp;rsquo; dilemma. Zhipu Web Search gives AI real-time web access, no more outdated knowledge. You could build custom AI workflows here, mixing maps, payment APIs, even blockchain functions. With 16,000+ tools aggregated, it’s a one-stop shop to supercharge your AI without digging through GitHub repos.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Browser Rendering: Cloud Headless Control</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/developers-bc5101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/developers-bc5101/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Cloudflare just dropped a game-changer by embedding headless browsers into their global network. Picture this: you kick back on your couch, send a command from your phone, and instantly capture webpage screenshots, generate PDFs, or automate full application testing—like having an invisible assistant operating in the cloud. I tested the screenshot feature, and the response was snappy as local execution, but with zero environment setup. The killer part? Dual integration with REST API for simple tasks and Workers Bindings for complex workflows. Perfect for data scraping, automated testing, or even converting webpages to Markdown. Content creators and devs are gonna love this.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Logo API: Brand Icons in Seconds</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/logo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/logo/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing solves what used to be a massive headache – fetching company logos. Remember manually searching for logos with inconsistent sizes and outdated versions? Now one API call delivers HD logos instantly, with global CDN ensuring they&amp;rsquo;re always current. Tried typing &amp;lsquo;apple.com&amp;rsquo; and got a perfect webp logo with retina support. Picture this: job boards auto-updating employer logos, finance platforms displaying real-time brand assets, zero designer overtime. Free to start, no barriers. Seriously slick.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>CheckCle: Sleek Monitoring Tool</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/x-luosays-52719431/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/x-luosays-52719431/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Seen my fair share of monitoring tools, but CheckCle&amp;rsquo;s open-source charm hits different. Its interface is so clean it feels like walking into a mission control center—real-time visibility into full-stack systems, apps, and infrastructure. Beyond tracking uptime and response speed, it even nags you about SSL certs. When services hiccup, alerts fire via email or Telegram instantly, with fault histories laid out like a storybook. Docker one-click setup? Few commands and you&amp;rsquo;re done. Browser access makes it feel like having an ops buddy on call 24/7. Tried it myself—could even spin up internal dashboards or treat alerts as daily digests. Seriously handy.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>