<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Freebie on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/freebie/</link><description>Recent content in Freebie on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:20:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/freebie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Engineer Pack: Ultimate Dev Toolkit</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/ai-engineer-pack-toolkit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/ai-engineer-pack-toolkit/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Exclusive deals
This is a curated collection of premium AI development tools offering exclusive discounts and free credits. It bundles together offerings from ElevenLabs, Mistral, Notion, and 50+ other leading platforms specifically for AI engineers and developers.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Substantial savings
Each tool provides significant value, like 3 free months of ElevenLabs Creator plan, $12k worth of Notion Business plan, and $2000 credits for e2b platform. These are deals that would be difficult to obtain individually and can save developers thousands of dollars.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Straightforward access
The website presents each tool&amp;rsquo;s offer in clear, concise cards showing exactly what you get and how much you save. No complicated signup process - just login and redeem the offers you need for your projects.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Zero technical barrier
Getting started requires minimal effort. Most offers are activated through redemption codes or automatic account upgrades. Perfect for developers at all levels looking to experiment with different AI tools without financial risk.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Superthread Free Lifetime Pro for 48h</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/superthread-lifetime-pro-freebie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/superthread-lifetime-pro-freebie/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Lifetime access
This is an all-in-one project management platform combining task boards, project tracking, team wiki, and sprint management in a single super fast interface.
Workflow unification
Centralizes disparate tools into one slick workflow, saving significant time and bringing back the joy of ticket creation according to engineering teams.
Clean interface
Features an intuitive design with unlimited boards, timeline layouts, and real-time collaboration that makes team coordination effortless.
Zero commitment
Get started in minutes without credit card, upgrade with code 10K-CELEBRATION for lifetime Pro access during this 48-hour celebration.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>