<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Article on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/article/</link><description>Recent content in Article on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 07:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LXGW Klee Simplified: Open Source Chinese Typeface</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/lxgw-klee-simplified-chinese/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/lxgw-klee-simplified-chinese/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="article-summary">Article Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Handcrafted Simplification
This article details the development process of LXGW Klee Simplified typeface. Based on the Japanese Klee font from FONTWORKS, the author manually completed 3500 commonly used simplified Chinese characters, creating this open-source typeface that combines features of regular and imitation Song styles.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Consistency Challenges
The biggest challenge was maintaining consistency with the original font style. By deconstructing strokes and assembling components, the author carefully adjusted each character to ensure the added simplified characters blend perfectly with the original font, avoiding awkwardness when mixing different typefaces.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Elegant Readability
What makes this font special is its preservation of elegant Japanese textbook-style brush strokes while conforming to Chinese reading habits. Each character undergoes repeated refinement with harmonious stroke structures, providing comfortable reading experience especially for long texts.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Open Source Accessibility
Although the author claims to be a non-professional type designer, the completion level is surprisingly high. The completely open-source project, handmade with FontCreator, avoids copyright risks and is free for anyone to use and modify.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="recommendation-reasons">Recommendation Reasons&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>JSON Prompt: Master Precise AI Outputs</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/json-prompt-guide-mpgone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/json-prompt-guide-mpgone/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="article-summary">Article Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Structured Precision
This comprehensive guide demonstrates how JSON formatting revolutionizes AI prompting, delivering consistent and accurate results. The author shares proven methodologies from enterprise implementations that reduce AI errors by 60%.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Real-World Impact
Through comparative case studies, the article shows JSON prompts&amp;rsquo; superiority over traditional text prompts. Companies save thousands of automation hours in content generation and video production workflows.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Accessible Implementation
Even without programming experience, users can create their first JSON prompt within 5 minutes. The guide provides complete learning paths from basic syntax to enterprise-level deployment.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Cutting-Edge Integration
Covers latest industry trends including integration with advanced AI models like Veo3. The article represents a significant evolution in AI interaction methodologies worth mastering.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="recommendation-reasons">Recommendation Reasons&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Mastering Veo3 Video Prompts</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/veo3-prompt-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/veo3-prompt-guide/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="article-summary">Article Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This comprehensive guide reveals the art of crafting effective prompts for Google&amp;rsquo;s Veo 3 video generation model. The article provides tested frameworks and real-world examples that consistently produce professional results.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Proven Examples
Three fully detailed prompt examples cover character storytelling, product showcases, and social media content. Each example includes specific camera movements, lighting requirements, and audio cues for different use cases.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Technical Precision
The guide emphasizes precise cinematography language and lighting terminology. Using terms like &amp;ldquo;dolly-in&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;chiaroscuro lighting&amp;rdquo; allows exact control over AI-generated video output.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Practical Implementation
Includes credit management strategies and audio integration techniques. The native audio generation feature creates synchronized dialogue and ambient sounds automatically.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="recommendation-reasons">Recommendation Reasons&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Leonardo AI: Mastering VEO3 Prompts Guide</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/leonardo-veo3-prompt-guide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/leonardo-veo3-prompt-guide/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Product Intro
This is a website focused on Leonardo.ai, offering in-depth articles on using VEO3 prompts. It helps users master advanced prompt techniques to enhance AI interactions. The content targets practical applications, enabling quick adoption and maximizing tool potential.
Scenario Efficiency
In real-world use, it significantly improves content generation accuracy and efficiency. Whether for creation or design, users can save substantial time through optimized prompts. The tips in the article are directly applicable to daily workflows, making AI a powerful assistant.
Design Details
The site features a clean design that prioritizes content delivery with a smooth user experience. Free from distractions, it allows readers to quickly focus on core knowledge. This minimalist approach ensures an efficient and enjoyable learning process.
Technical Practicality
Technically, the article explains concepts in an accessible way, even for beginners. It offers actionable advice that can be applied without complex setup. The low learning curve delivers immediate practical value.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>