<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marketing on FindSoFun - Discover Interesting AI Tools &amp; Frontend Libraries</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/marketing/</link><description>Recent content in Marketing on FindSoFun - Discover Interesting AI Tools &amp; Frontend Libraries</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Semrush Blog: AI Search Marketing Hub</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/semrush-f7aa5e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/semrush-f7aa5e/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Opening Semrush Blog feels like walking into a digital marketing arsenal where every article is live ammunition. I was struggling with AI search ranking yesterday, and today they drop a fresh August guide on tracking Google AI Mode visibility – even predicting 2025 trends. This isn&amp;rsquo;t dry theory; it&amp;rsquo;s hands-on instructions using Semrush tools to analyze competitors and track rankings. They even dare to expose industry pricing secrets like Local SEO costs. Feels like a daily tactical manual for marketing teams, while beginners can follow the step-by-step guides. Perfect for staying ahead in the AI search game.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>reGrowth: Competitor Intel Unleashed</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/regrowth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/regrowth/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is slick! Picture yourself watching every move your competitors make on X—real-time follower growth, engagement spikes, viral content—all laid bare. No more guessing what works; just see which posts blew up and replicate the magic. I tried it and felt like having a backstage pass to their strategy meetings, even accessing analytics they don&amp;rsquo;t see themselves. Set alerts for instant notifications when competitors gain traction, so you never miss a trend. For content creators and marketers, this tool could slash your testing time by 80%. It&amp;rsquo;s like having a spy agency for your niche.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>SEOMato: 30s SEO Health Check</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/seomato/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/seomato/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is legit! Just tested my blog and got a detailed report in 30 seconds flat - it even caught missing alt tags on images. No signup nonsense, just drop a URL and go. Feels like giving your site a quick CT scan. The priority ranking is killer: shows exactly what needs fixing now versus later. I even ran competitor sites through it and instantly understood their ranking secrets. For a free tool, the depth of analysis is borderline ridiculous.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Skale: Conversion-Focused Design Consult</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/skale-1b22b4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/skale-1b22b4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When I landed on this booking page, my first thought was: this is exactly the emergency room for overwhelmed product managers and founders. A 30-minute call specifically targeting low website conversion rates and mediocre design. Picture this: you just pulled an all-nighter tweaking prototypes, then Skale feels like having a design veteran whisper &amp;lsquo;Stop struggling, I got this&amp;rsquo;. With over 60 startups served, they&amp;rsquo;re not some fluffy design studio but actually pack your business goals into a website. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried similar services – it&amp;rsquo;s like giving your site an adrenaline shot. Honestly saw landing page click-through rates jump. If you&amp;rsquo;re battling SaaS customer acquisition or are a digital creator wanting to elevate brand质感, these 30 minutes might be more valuable than a month of trial and error.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Ahrefs: SEO Mastery Guide</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/ahrefs-bd4b5e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/ahrefs-bd4b5e/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Opening this SEO guide feels like having an expert sitting right beside you. It breaks down everything from how search engines work to keyword analysis in digestible steps. I tried their technical SEO section and it&amp;rsquo;s like getting personalized coaching - even cookie settings are explained in detail. The glossary is a lifesaver when you encounter unfamiliar terms. When I hit writer&amp;rsquo;s block, their content optimization section always sparks new ideas. Perfect for training new team members or as a daily SEO checklist.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Canny: Smarter Feedback Management</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/canny/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/canny/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Picture this: all those scattered user feedback from emails, chats, and support tickets get automatically captured, deduped, and organized by AI—plus it even asks follow-up questions to clarify needs. Canny feels like having a tireless assistant curating your feedback hub. I tried their Autopilot feature; it snagged casual user complaints from Slack and generated priority scores instantly. The killer part? Building public roadmaps so users see their ideas in action—this alone cuts down support tickets dramatically. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a startup saving PM hours or a large company syncing cross-team insights, it&amp;rsquo;s a game-changer.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>