<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advanced Technology on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/advanced-technology/</link><description>Recent content in Advanced Technology on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/advanced-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kurzgesagt: Animated Science Digest</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-18c5d328/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-18c5d328/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Click into this channel and you are diving into a kaleidoscope of science where complex ideas are broken down with vibrant animation and storytelling. The team calls themselves optimistic nihilists but explains cosmic and biological concepts like a friend chatting over coffee. I was watching their CRISPR episode yesterday - they compared gene editing to molecular scissors and it just clicked. Even used nuclear flies to explain immune system? Who thinks of that. Perfect for bedtime learning or kids science启蒙. Bonus: it doubles as English listening practice with 24M subscribers vouching for it.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Browserfly: AI Assistant in Your Browser</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/browserfly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/browserfly/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Picture this: an AI sidekick living right in your browser, no virtual machines or new browsers needed. Just tell it &amp;lsquo;summarize this page&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;fill out this form&amp;rsquo;, and it operates like a human would. I tried the auto-form feature – felt like having a personal assistant handling tedious tasks. You can even click any element to analyze or modify it through natural language. Imagine using it for email sorting or research automation. This isn&amp;rsquo;t another browser; it&amp;rsquo;s your existing Chrome/Edge upgraded to a smart workstation.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Semrush Blog: AI Search Marketing Hub</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/semrush-f7aa5e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/semrush-f7aa5e/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Opening Semrush Blog feels like walking into a digital marketing arsenal where every article is live ammunition. I was struggling with AI search ranking yesterday, and today they drop a fresh August guide on tracking Google AI Mode visibility – even predicting 2025 trends. This isn&amp;rsquo;t dry theory; it&amp;rsquo;s hands-on instructions using Semrush tools to analyze competitors and track rankings. They even dare to expose industry pricing secrets like Local SEO costs. Feels like a daily tactical manual for marketing teams, while beginners can follow the step-by-step guides. Perfect for staying ahead in the AI search game.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Fast3D: AI 3D in Seconds</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/fast3d-81e321/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/fast3d-81e321/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is wild—feed it an image or text, and it spits out textured 3D models in under 10 seconds, no login required. I tossed in a rough sofa sketch, and bam: professional-grade assets with adjustable mesh density and photorealistic PBR materials. Perfect for designers rapid-prototyping, game devs批量-generating props, or even 3D printing enthusiasts saving hours of modeling. The multi-view input feature is a game-changer for accuracy, like having a 24/7 modeling assistant that never sleeps.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>ElevenLabs: Human-Level AI Voice Generator</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/start-64ffb4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/start-64ffb4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>First time I heard AI voice without getting creeped out – natural breaths and pauses in 32 languages across thousands of voices. Cloned my own voice reading a novel and my wife thought someone was in the room. Video creators must try the dubbing feature, localizing content in 29 languages feels like hiring pro voice actors. API integration is stupid simple – went from manually tweaking voice params to having AI agents handle customer inquiries overnight. Long-form audio editing is a gamechanger for podcast editing without retakes.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Genie 3: Real-Time World Simulator</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/deepmind-349c66/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/deepmind-349c66/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is wild—type a text prompt and it instantly generates interactive 3D worlds running at 24fps. Picture describing a volcanic terrain and watching a wheeled robot crunch through blackened rocks with lava flowing in the distance. I tested &amp;lsquo;jetski during festival of lights&amp;rsquo; and got dynamic water reflections in seconds. Perfect for AI training, prototyping, or quickly building VR scenes without tearing your hair out over manual modeling.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Qoder: AI Coding Partner</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/qoder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/qoder/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This ain&amp;rsquo;t your average AI coding toy - it&amp;rsquo;s like having a senior dev reading your mind. Toss a spec into Quest Mode and watch it autonomously plan, code, and test asynchronously. Tried its code explanation feature? It reverse-engineers your entire architecture like Sherlock with a keyboard. The MCP integration feels like giving your IDE superpowers. Suddenly unit tests and code searches become conversations instead of chores.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Runway: AI Creativity Unleashed</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/runwayml/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/runwayml/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Open Runway and step into a futuristic creative lab—type a sentence, and AI instantly generates ad photos, cinematic videos, or even designs a full living room. I tried &amp;lsquo;dramatic aerial shot of NYC&amp;rsquo; and got Hollywood-level footage in seconds, like hiring a pro team. It also crafts music videos, partners with film festivals, and packs AI creativity into everyone&amp;rsquo;s hands. Imagine small brands whipping up marketing assets, creators shooting low-budget shorts, or schools making visual content—all possible here.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Claude Code: AI Coding Co-pilot</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/deeplearning-a8c56f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/deeplearning-a8c56f/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This isn&amp;rsquo;t just another code completion tool - it&amp;rsquo;s like having a senior dev sitting next to you. Claude Code actually understands your codebase architecture, remembers project context across sessions, and can work on multiple features simultaneously. The MCP server integration is genius: pull designs directly from Figma, automate browser testing with Playwright, and watch it refactor Jupyter notebooks into production dashboards. Tried it on the RAG chatbot project and felt like I had a tireless coding partner handling planning, testing, and debugging. Can see this being killer for onboarding new hires or firefighting production issues.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>MirageLSD: Real-Time Video Alchemist</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/miragelsd-81e321/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/miragelsd-81e321/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing reminds me of the first time I used Photoshop, but in real-time. You turn on your camera and instantly the real world transforms into an anime scene, with latency so low you barely feel it. Imagine streaming with your background suddenly becoming a cyberpunk city, or converting game footage into oil painting style in real-time. I tried it with my phone camera - that instant feedback feels like adding a filter to reality, but way smarter. It understands the content, maintains temporal consistency without flickering. Could see this being huge for virtual meetings or making educational videos more engaging by instantly changing styles.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>OpenHunts: Product Discovery Playground</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/openhunts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/openhunts/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking into OpenHunts feels like entering a tech toy store where new gadgets drop daily. The countdown for Nexty&amp;rsquo;s launch got me hooked instantly. From practical tools like Peerlist internships to mind-blowing AI assistants like Clearo, every discovery feels like unwrapping a present. The voting system is genius - casting 3 daily votes makes you feel like a product judge. Real founder endorsements add authentic credibility. Perfect for competitive research or finding your next dev tool. The community vibe is palpable, like being at a startup demo day every day.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Hillsdale Online: Elite Courses Zero Cost</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/online-4878aa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/online-4878aa/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Step into a digital library where Ivy League-level professors break down Western civilization&amp;rsquo;s greatest hits—from Aristotle to the U.S. Constitution—all for free. Tried Constitution 101 and felt like having a scholar whispering insights during my commute. Perfect for night owls craving depth or parents homeschooling with classic literature. No paywalls, just pure knowledge infusion.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>OrbStack: Docker Desktop Killer</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/orbstack/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/orbstack/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Remember Docker Desktop draining your Mac&amp;rsquo;s battery? OrbStack is like swapping a clunky truck for a sports car. Containers run natively smooth on M1/M2 chips, launching in seconds while doubling battery life. I tested building environments - 17 minutes instead of 45, and I could actually work while compiling. Rosetta x86 emulation, VirtioFS file sharing, all the tech magic is here with seamless CLI integration. VPN and IPv6 just work. The killer feature? Background CPU usage under 0.1% and only 10MB disk space - it&amp;rsquo;s like having an invisible assistant. Now I code without fan noise, finally experiencing what Apple silicon development should feel like.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>