<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UI on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/ui/</link><description>Recent content in UI on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/ui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notioly: Notion-Style Illustration Library</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/notioly-notion-illustrations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/notioly-notion-illustrations/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>SVG Collection
Notioly offers over 200 Notion-style vector illustrations with monthly updates. All assets are in scalable SVG format, available in free and premium versions. The library covers diverse usage scenarios for digital products.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Comprehensive Scenes
From office collaboration to daily life, illustrations include team meetings, remote work, studying, and 200+ specific scenarios. Each design comes with clear context descriptions for easy selection.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Consistent Aesthetic
Maintains Notion&amp;rsquo;s minimalist aesthetic with clean lines and restrained colors. Character designs are cute yet professional, with balanced compositions that fit modern digital products.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Easy Customization
SVG format allows direct code editing for color changes and element adjustments. Ready to use without installation, compatible with major design tools and development environments.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Phosphor Icons: Design Essential Toolkit</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/phosphor-icons-ui/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/phosphor-icons-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Free icon library
This is a high-quality free icon library providing rich vector icon resources for designers and developers. The icons feature consistent and refined styling, covering various common scenarios and industry needs, completely open source and commercially usable.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Workflow efficiency
In practical projects, whether doing interface design, creating presentations, or drawing flowcharts, you can quickly find suitable icons. Directly copy SVG code or download PNG files, significantly improving workflow efficiency without wasting time searching for icons.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Visual excellence
Icon design details are exceptionally well-handled with smooth lines and proportional harmony, maintaining clarity at different sizes. Supports multiple styles and weight variations, easily matching various design aesthetics with professional visual effects.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Developer friendly
Technically very accessible with support for React, Vue and other framework component integrations. Documentation is clear and easy to understand. Customizing colors and sizes is straightforward with zero learning curve, enabling developers to quickly integrate into projects.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Canny: Smarter Feedback Management</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/canny-feedback-saas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/canny-feedback-saas/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Feedback Centralization
Automatically captures user feedback from multiple channels and intelligently deduplicates entries. Provides a unified platform to organize feature requests and customer insights without manual tracking.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Workflow Integration
Seamlessly connects with popular tools like Jira, Slack, and Intercom. Enables teams to prioritize features using customizable scoring formulas based on impact and effort metrics.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Clean Interface
Features an intuitive dashboard that makes feedback analysis accessible to entire teams. Customizable portals maintain brand consistency while collecting user input.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>AI Automation
Leverages machine learning to summarize comments, suggest replies, and identify duplicate submissions. Setup takes minutes with no technical expertise required.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>PaperCSS: Informal Style Framework</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/paper-css-framework/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/paper-css-framework/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Handwritten aesthetic
This CSS framework adds handwritten paper texture to web interfaces, moving away from cold technical appearance. It creates unique visual experiences by simulating paper grain and natural strokes. Perfect for projects needing warm human touch.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Quick integration
Start using it immediately through CDN without complex configuration. Provides complete component library including buttons, cards, forms and layout systems. Clear documentation helps build distinctive pages within minutes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Design philosophy
Embraces informal aesthetics with slightly irregular and hand-drawn elements. Borders aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect straight lines, shadows have natural diffusion, color combinations feel warm and comfortable. This approach makes interfaces more human and approachable.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Lightweight technology
Built with pure CSS without JavaScript dependencies. Supports custom SASS variables for easy style adjustments. Simple build process with npm installation and source compilation options, suitable for various development needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Real-time GitHub Icon Library Trends</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/getstack-iconset-trends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/getstack-iconset-trends/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>GitHub Data Insights
This platform tracks icon library usage trends across GitHub repositories, providing real-time data on popularity and changes in the open source ecosystem.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Weekly Updates
Data refreshes weekly showing which libraries are rising or declining, like Tabler gaining 4 repos this week while React Icons slightly decreased, offering valuable reference for tech stack decisions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Clean Interface
Extremely minimalist design presents data through rankings and trend charts without distractions, with quick search functionality to locate specific icon libraries seamlessly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Zero Barrier
Completely free access without registration required, using authentic GitHub data to help developers quickly get the latest technology selection references.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>BuouUI: TailwindCSS UI Library</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/buouui-tailwind-ui-library/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/buouui-tailwind-ui-library/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ready Components
BuouUI is a TailwindCSS-based library offering components, sections, and templates for Next.js and React projects. It integrates Server Components and Radix UI for high performance and accessibility. Developers can copy-paste code directly, speeding up integration and reducing development time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Efficiency Boost
In practice, pre-built components cover forms, tables, modals, and more, minimizing redundant coding. The team, with backgrounds from Tencent and Huawei, ensures battle-tested components that accelerate project iterations. Real-time collaboration and multi-language support make it ideal for teams.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Design Excellence
The UI focuses on aesthetics and functionality, with smooth animations like particle clocks and step forms. Styles range from brutal retro to modern marketing elements, maintaining visual consistency. User feedback highlights its high-end, elegant, and customizable themes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tech Friendly
Built on TailwindCSS, it requires no extra learning curve; code embeds seamlessly. Starter kits and documentation ease onboarding, with features like end-to-end encryption and cloud sync. The open-source community regularly updates with new components.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Tailwind Plus: UI Components Treasure</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tailwindcss-plus-604652/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/tailwindcss-plus-604652/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Dev Velocity
Built by the creators of Tailwind CSS, this component library doubles frontend development efficiency. With 500+ professionally designed components covering marketing pages, application UIs, and e-commerce scenarios, you can copy-paste ready-to-use blocks. Even complex page modules can be assembled quickly, eliminating the pain of designing from scratch.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Visual Craft
Every component is polished by professional design teams, with responsive layouts and interaction details handled impeccably. From hero sections to pricing tables, even 404 pages are tailored for real-world projects. Using these components instantly elevates your project&amp;rsquo;s visual quality.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tech Excellence
Templates built with React and Next.js aren&amp;rsquo;t just finished products—they&amp;rsquo;re textbooks for learning Tailwind best practices. The Catalyst UI kit demonstrates how to build reusable component systems with clear,借鉴-worthy code structure. The one-time purchase includes lifetime updates, offering superb long-term value.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Flowbite: Tailwind UI Kit</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/flowbite-tailwind-ui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/flowbite-tailwind-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking into Flowbite feels like browsing a design supermarket—600+ UI components built with Tailwind CSS utility classes. I dragged a button component, copied the code, and styled it instantly. Dark mode? It auto-switches with your system. RTL support for Arabic and Hebrew handles logical properties smoothly. The Figma sync is a game-changer, ending designer-dev battles. Perfect for whipping up admin dashboards or marketing pages by stacking blocks. Frontend folks will hug this.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Preline: Ultimate Tailwind Component Library</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/preline-tailwind-ui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/preline-tailwind-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The moment you open Preline, it feels like stepping into a treasure trove for frontend developers. 840+ components neatly organized - from buttons to tables, navbars to date pickers, everything you need. The killer feature is full framework compatibility: switch between React and Vue seamlessly, with dark mode built-in. I tried their Figma design system and it perfectly mirrors the code components, finally ending the designer-developer blame game. Check the user wall comments - everyone&amp;rsquo;s asking &amp;lsquo;How is this free?&amp;rsquo;. Seriously, this quality would be paid elsewhere. If you use Tailwind, this thing will double your development efficiency, saving enough time for countless coffee breaks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>daisyUI: Tailwind Components Revolution</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/daisyui-tailwind-plugin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/daisyui-tailwind-plugin/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Ever tired of writing endless Tailwind utility classes? daisyUI hits you with semantic names like &amp;lsquo;btn&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;card&amp;rsquo; that slash code volume by 88%. I tried building a form - what used to take 20 lines now takes 3, like liposuction for your HTML. Swap between 30+ themes with one click, from cyberpunk to pastel, no more team fights over styling. Best part? Pure CSS with zero JS dependency, works in any framework. Even my PM could tweak components without breaking a sweat.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Spectrum UI: Copy-Paste React Components</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/spectrum-ui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/spectrum-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Stumbled upon this gem while wrestling with UI deadlines – it&amp;rsquo;s like finding a pre-built Lego set for web devs. Over 250 production-ready components built with Tailwind CSS and Next.js, just copy-paste and tweak. Tried their login block and payment form: no more fighting with CSS at 3 AM. Open source, Vercel-backed, and free. Perfect for startups rushing MVPs or solo devs side projects. Feels like having a design team in your clipboard.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Aceternity UI: Motion Component Library</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/aceternity-ui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/aceternity-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is pure gold for frontend developers! Browsing the site feels like walking through a component supermarket where every animation is ready to grab. I tried the card stack effect - copied the code and within minutes my page came alive. No more wrestling with CSS animations, Framer Motion does the heavy lifting. Perfect for building portfolio sites, corporate pages, or interactive marketing landings. The community buzz is insane, they even included Elon Musk parody cards. These folks know how to make development fun.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>shadcn/ui: Design System Foundation</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/shadcn-ui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/shadcn-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking into shadcn/ui feels like browsing a component boutique – every calendar, button, and form is so polished you just want to drag them into your project. I tried their calendar component; the custom color schemes and smooth interactions rival paid libraries. Perfect for whipping up enterprise dashboards or personal trackers without reinventing the wheel. All code is open and modifiable, no lock-in nonsense. My go-to for auth flows and data panels now.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Animate UI: Copy-Paste Motion Magic</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/animate-ui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/animate-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This ain&amp;rsquo;t your grandma&amp;rsquo;s UI library - it&amp;rsquo;s like a component buffet where you grab animated React pieces directly. Tried the cursor follower that dances with your mouse movements, instantly turning dull admin panels into interactive playgrounds. Open-source and free, it plays nice with Shadcn UI like peanut butter and jelly. Toss a fireworks background with typewriter text effects and boom - you&amp;rsquo;ve got a pro landing page in minutes. Perfect for indie devs who want to impress clients without breaking the bank.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Ark UI: Cross-Framework Component Library</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/ark-ui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/ark-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is slick! 45+ headless components that snap together like LEGO. Tried their Slider component - state machine driven smoothness with crystal clear code. The zero-styling approach is genius: blank canvas ready for your design system without any fights. Supports React, Vue, Solid, Svelte out of the box. Finally got our multi-framework team working together seamlessly. Seeing Chakra UI and OVHCloud using it gives me confidence. Perfect for building enterprise design systems or component libraries for open source projects. Solid stuff!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>HeroUI: Modern React UI Revolution</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/heroui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/heroui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>HeroUI hits different—it’s like giving your React projects a designer’s touch without the headache. Built on Tailwind CSS, it ditches runtime styles for lean bundles. Dark mode? Flips automatically like your phone’s OS. Theming is a config file away: go minimalist, retro, or wild with colors. I tweaked that Confetti button—stupid simple code, insane results. This library isn’t just functional; it’s fun. Perfect for team consistency, portfolio polish, or whipping up a nav site or inbox UI fast. Plus, React Aria under the hood means accessibility out-of-the-box. Respect.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>SuperBrowserWindowKit: Native macOS Effects for Electron</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/bytemyth-2998ae/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/bytemyth-2998ae/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Electron developers, this is a game-changer! Just tried this toolkit and it instantly gives your apps that premium macOS native feel. The custom rounded corners blend seamlessly with the system aesthetics, no more CSS hacking. The liquid glass effect is pure magic - that translucent sidebar with depth perception elevates your app&amp;rsquo;s sophistication. Integration is stupid simple, just a few lines of code. Perfect for SaaS dashboards or design tools. Only caveat: test license won&amp;rsquo;t work in production, need commercial license for real deployment.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>KokonutUI: 100+ Open Source Components</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/kokonutui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/kokonutui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking into KokonutUI feels like browsing a design supermarket where every component is pre-packaged and ready to use. I tried a few buttons and cards – the motion effects are so smooth it&amp;rsquo;s like they&amp;rsquo;ve got built-in springs. Perfect for frontend devs tired of reinventing wheels or designers on tight deadlines. Used it for a weekend side project and doubled my interface building speed. My boss even asked if I&amp;rsquo;d been working overtime. With custom themes, the possibilities are endless.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Magic UI: Motion Component Library</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/magicui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/magicui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Cracking open Magic UI feels like walking into a designer&amp;rsquo;s secret arsenal - 150+ free animated components ready to rock your landing pages. I tried their file preview component and the drag interaction was smoother than butter. Seeing YC startups actually use this in production? That&amp;rsquo;s when you know it&amp;rsquo;s legit. Plus it plays nice with shadcn/ui, saving frontend devs hours of tinkering time.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Origin UI: Copy-Paste Components</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/originui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/originui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking into Origin UI feels like browsing a design supermarket—shelves packed with ready-to-use Tailwind CSS and React components. I tried their collection of 54 button variants and instantly felt frontend development shift from handmade to assembly line. Free, open-source, and no watermark? It is basically a cheat code for indie devs. Imagine hitting ⌘K to search components when PMs rush for UI updates, delivering in five minutes flat. Plus, it is perfect for whipping up internal tools or demo projects. How is that for a power move?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Spotted: Design Inspiration Hub</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/t-002b64/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/t-002b64/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Browsing this site feels like peeking behind the curtains of top products, with 517 real interface clips laid bare. I skimmed through messaging designs and instantly understood why some apps just feel right. The categorization is incredibly detailed—from motion graphics to design languages, even team types are sorted. Designers never have to scavenge the web for inspiration again. Perfect for building your personal design library when hitting creative blocks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Kigen: Smart Color Engine</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/kigen-eed2ed/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/kigen-eed2ed/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Slide the algorithm intensity bar and watch 11 perfect shades magically generate—with automatic CSS variables and Tailwind tokens ready to copy-paste. I created a spring-green palette in seconds, plugged it into Figma, and my design system instantly came alive. No more guessing hex codes or calculating contrast ratios. Want to build brand palettes? Check accessibility? Even craft dynamic gradients? This tool bends to your will like digital clay.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>TweakCN: Shadcn Style Playground</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/x-vikingmute-70803761/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/x-vikingmute-70803761/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of Shadcn&amp;rsquo;s default look, TweakCN is your theme playground. With hundreds of pre-built themes like the whimsical Kodama Grove, it transforms your component library in seconds. No complex setup—just copy-paste CSS variables and watch your project come alive. I browse themes like scrolling through a design catalog before starting any new project. Perfect for quickly prototyping different visual styles or giving legacy projects a fresh coat of paint. The freedom it offers is downright addictive.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>RetroUI: Vintage React Components</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/retroui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/retroui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The moment I landed on RetroUI, the retro-meets-modern vibe hooked me. Components are copy-paste ready—no CSS wrestling. I tweaked their buttons and badges like changing outfits, all thanks to Tailwind&amp;rsquo;s flexibility. Picture building a nostalgic dashboard or a personal nav site in minutes, with type-safe code that just feels clean. The community&amp;rsquo;s growing with 650+ stars and a buzzing Discord, perfect for riding the retro wave with fellow devs.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Tailwind Plus: UI Treasure Chest</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tailwindcss-604652/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/tailwindcss-604652/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The official Tailwind CSS team dropped a component goldmine – 500+ polished pieces ready to drag and drop. I tried their marketing sections and built a landing page in minutes that would normally take hours. Perfect for developers racing against deadlines or beginners wanting to learn pro-level Tailwind techniques. You can even reverse-engineer their code structure to teach your AI assistant how to write better components.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>