<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Doc on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/doc/</link><description>Recent content in Doc on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/doc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WonderPen: Professional Writing App for Authors</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/wonderpen-writing-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/wonderpen-writing-app/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A desktop writing application designed for long-form content creation, supporting novels, papers, diaries and various writing scenarios.
Tree-structured directory management organizes lengthy works clearly, offline-first design ensures uninterrupted writing, and cloud sync enables seamless multi-device workflow.
Minimalist and focus modes eliminate distractions, typewriter mode keeps cursor centered, whiteboard and cards facilitate idea recording and writing planning.
Markdown support, one-click formatting, and auto-replace features enhance writing efficiency, while data backup and version snapshots provide double protection for your work.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>All-in-One PDF Toolkit for Every Document Need</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/pdf-all-in-one-toolkit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/pdf-all-in-one-toolkit/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Comprehensive PDF processing platform
This web-based tool offers complete PDF solutions from basic editing to advanced processing. It supports 50+ functions including format conversion, page management, and security features, all working directly in your browser without installation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Real-world document workflow efficiency
Merge multiple PDFs or extract specific pages with simple drag-and-drop operations. Convert Office documents to PDF while preserving formatting integrity. The OCR feature accurately processes scanned documents, making digital archiving effortless.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Clean and intuitive interface design
The minimalist interface features clear functional categorization and intuitive navigation. Dark mode reduces eye strain during extended document work sessions. Responsive design ensures smooth operation even with large files.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Local processing and privacy protection
All operations occur locally in your browser, ensuring files never leave your device. Supports 40+ language interfaces. Free version covers most daily needs, while pro version unlocks batch processing and advanced capabilities.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>iGenFlow: Auto-Create Tutorials from Screen Actions</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/igenflow-automated-docs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/igenflow-automated-docs/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Automatically captures every step of web operation and generates illustrated guides in real-time. Just perform tasks normally, and it produces clear, easy-to-follow documentation without manual writing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Perfect for product documentation, customer support, and knowledge base management. Significantly improves efficiency in employee training, software reviews, and content creation, reducing manual effort by 80%.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Simple interface with one-click recording, intelligently tracks mouse clicks and keyboard inputs. Accurately identifies action areas, captures screenshots, and adds descriptions seamlessly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Install Chrome or Edge extension to start. Supports exporting to PDF, Word, and other formats. Flexible editing allows adding or deleting steps, and sharing via links enhances collaboration.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Veo3 AI Video Generation Prompt Guide</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/vertex-ai-veo-prompt-guide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/vertex-ai-veo-prompt-guide/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Text-to-Video Magic
Google Vertex AI&amp;rsquo;s Veo model transforms text descriptions into high-quality videos. Simply input prompts to generate various video styles, from cinematic scenes to cartoon animations with ease.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Boost创作效率
No professional editing skills required—just describe your vision to quickly produce video content. Ideal for content creators, marketers, and educators to create visual materials efficiently, significantly reducing production time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Precision提示控制
Achieve accurate video results by detailing subjects, contexts, actions, and styles. Adjust camera motions, compositions, and ambiance to match your creative intent perfectly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Safety过滤保障
Built-in safety filters automatically block违规内容, ensuring generated videos adhere to responsible AI guidelines. Reporting channels are available to maintain a healthy创作环境.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>