<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Doc on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/doc/</link><description>Recent content in Doc on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:47:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/doc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>iGenFlow: Auto-Create Tutorials from Screen Actions</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/igenflow-automated-docs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/igenflow-automated-docs/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Automatically captures every step of web operation and generates illustrated guides in real-time. Just perform tasks normally, and it produces clear, easy-to-follow documentation without manual writing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Perfect for product documentation, customer support, and knowledge base management. Significantly improves efficiency in employee training, software reviews, and content creation, reducing manual effort by 80%.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Simple interface with one-click recording, intelligently tracks mouse clicks and keyboard inputs. Accurately identifies action areas, captures screenshots, and adds descriptions seamlessly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Install Chrome or Edge extension to start. Supports exporting to PDF, Word, and other formats. Flexible editing allows adding or deleting steps, and sharing via links enhances collaboration.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Veo3 AI Video Generation Prompt Guide</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/vertex-ai-veo-prompt-guide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/vertex-ai-veo-prompt-guide/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Text-to-Video Magic
Google Vertex AI&amp;rsquo;s Veo model transforms text descriptions into high-quality videos. Simply input prompts to generate various video styles, from cinematic scenes to cartoon animations with ease.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Boost创作效率
No professional editing skills required—just describe your vision to quickly produce video content. Ideal for content creators, marketers, and educators to create visual materials efficiently, significantly reducing production time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Precision提示控制
Achieve accurate video results by detailing subjects, contexts, actions, and styles. Adjust camera motions, compositions, and ambiance to match your creative intent perfectly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Safety过滤保障
Built-in safety filters automatically block违规内容, ensuring generated videos adhere to responsible AI guidelines. Reporting channels are available to maintain a healthy创作环境.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>