<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>English Learning on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/english-learning/</link><description>Recent content in English Learning on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/english-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Luke's Podcast: Learn English Through Detective Stories</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-icm6ai1kpaa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-icm6ai1kpaa/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Step into a Victorian detective agency where you learn English by solving mysteries. Peter Carlson&amp;rsquo;s text adventure comes alive with Luke&amp;rsquo;s authentic British narration—you make choices, unravel clues, and absorb the language naturally. Tried it during my commute and felt like having a storytelling session with a London native. The interactive format beats textbook drills any day, perfect for auditory learners who hate memorization. Great for bedtime listening too—who says learning can&amp;rsquo;t be fun?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Julebu: Addictive English Learning</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/julebu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/julebu/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This app turns English learning into a genuine game! Open it and you are solving puzzles - each long sentence broken into building blocks waiting to be reconstructed. Four modes keep it fresh: translation challenges, listening comprehension like sound hunting, dictation speed tests, and pronunciation practice. The magic is in the i+1 theory, always staying just slightly above your level, like a game level you almost beat, making you crave one more try. I tried the IELTS course - boring complex sentences became engaging puzzles, and before I knew it, I had memorized advanced expressions. Perfect for interview prep or crushing a few sentences during your commute. The progress dashboard shows your improvement curve, and you can even customize voice gender and playback speed - details matter.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Spokenly: Offline Dictation Master</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/spokenly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/spokenly/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing hits different—just click and talk, words appear instantly without touching the keyboard. Tried dictating code in Xcode, response is as fast as typing, with auto-switching for 100+ languages. Privacy is rock-solid: local models process everything on-device, zero data leaks. Agent mode is a game-changer—control your Mac with voice commands, search web or launch apps hands-free. History with search and playback means no lost ideas. Free local models cover basics, Pro at $7.99/mo unlocks cloud features. No fluff, pure productivity.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Fluently: AI English Coach</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/getfluently/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/getfluently/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is legit! Picture this: you&amp;rsquo;re in a crucial English meeting, stumbling over words, and an AI whispers the right phrasing in real-time—that&amp;rsquo;s Fluently. Tried their mock interview feature and it felt like having a native speaker drilling with me, catching every pronunciation slip and grammar hiccup. The killer feature? It plugs directly into your actual calls, fixing mistakes on the fly. Available 24/7 at 1/15 the cost of human tutors. Game-changer for non-native professionals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>