<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Job on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/job/</link><description>Recent content in Job on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:39:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Foorilla: Real-Time Job Platform for Coders</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/foorilla-jobs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/foorilla-jobs/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Global Job Aggregation
This is a career platform dedicated to technical talents, aggregating global coding, building, and hacker roles. It uses smart crawlers to update job data in real-time, covering full-time, remote, and internship types. The service focuses exclusively on developers, engineers, and makers, filtering out non-tech noise.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Efficient Filtering Export
Users can quickly filter jobs by tech stack, region, and time range, with options to save custom searches. CSV or JSON export simplifies batch applications or analysis, reducing repetitive tasks. For frequent job seekers or freelancers, this significantly speeds up the hunt.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Minimalist UI Design
The interface adopts a command-line style with no distractions, emphasizing job listings. Real-time tags like &amp;lsquo;1h ago&amp;rsquo; and salary ranges are displayed directly, minimizing clicks. Dark theme and monospace fonts align with developer tool habits, ensuring intuitive operation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tech-Friendly Integration
The platform offers API-like filtering and export, suitable for automation scripts. Zero learning curve—browse without registration, though saving searches requires an account. Broad data coverage includes startups to enterprises, with multi-currency and language support.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>