<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Animation on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/animation/</link><description>Recent content in Animation on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/animation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create Videos with React Code</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/remotion-react-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/remotion-react-video/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Programmatic video creation
This tool enables developers to create real MP4 videos using React programming. It supports parameterized content, server-side rendering, and building complete video applications. You can produce professional video effects with familiar React syntax, fundamentally changing traditional video production workflows.
Dynamic content editing
In practice, you can dynamically adjust video content by passing data to parameterize video elements. It allows embedding videos into your own applications and building interactive interfaces around them. Supports local, server, or serverless rendering with output in MP4 and other formats for various scenarios.
React-based design
The entire stack is built on React technology, making it easy for developers to get started. Provides tools like Remotion Studio, Player, and Editor Starter with clean and intuitive interfaces. Features like dark mode adaptation and drag-and-drop sorting ensure smooth interactions comparable to professional video editing software.
Modern tech stack
Utilizes cutting-edge standards like WebCodecs for frontend video processing. Supports server-side and Lambda serverless rendering with strong scalability. Gentle learning curve allows React developers to start almost immediately, backed by rich community resources and professional support.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Kurzgesagt: Animated Science Digest</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-18c5d328/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-18c5d328/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Click into this channel and you are diving into a kaleidoscope of science where complex ideas are broken down with vibrant animation and storytelling. The team calls themselves optimistic nihilists but explains cosmic and biological concepts like a friend chatting over coffee. I was watching their CRISPR episode yesterday - they compared gene editing to molecular scissors and it just clicked. Even used nuclear flies to explain immune system? Who thinks of that. Perfect for bedtime learning or kids science启蒙. Bonus: it doubles as English listening practice with 24M subscribers vouching for it.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>HiAnime: Instant Anime Stream</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/hianime-4858da/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/hianime-4858da/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Open HiAnime and it feels like walking into a 24/7 anime mart—no sign-up, just click and watch. I tried streaming One Piece and it loaded instantly, with dual audio tracks toggling smoothly. Their mobile app lets you binge on the go, perfect for commutes. The community section buzzes with episode discussions, and you might stumble upon hidden gems. Feels like a daily go-to library for anime lovers, straightforward and reliable.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Storyset: Free Illustrations Animator</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/storyset/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/storyset/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Step into Storyset and it&amp;rsquo;s like unlocking a treasure chest of customizable illustrations—business, education, medical, you name it. The magic? Not just static images: tweak colors, swap backgrounds, and animate right in your browser. I tried spicing up a landing page and within minutes had a lively scene dancing on screen. Perfect for teams grinding on presentations, apps, or social content. And hey, it&amp;rsquo;s free. Seriously, why pay for stock art when you can play here?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Aceternity UI: Motion Component Library</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/aceternity-ui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/aceternity-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is pure gold for frontend developers! Browsing the site feels like walking through a component supermarket where every animation is ready to grab. I tried the card stack effect - copied the code and within minutes my page came alive. No more wrestling with CSS animations, Framer Motion does the heavy lifting. Perfect for building portfolio sites, corporate pages, or interactive marketing landings. The community buzz is insane, they even included Elon Musk parody cards. These folks know how to make development fun.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Animata: Plug-and-Play React Animations</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/animata/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/animata/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Stumbled upon Animata while rushing a client project and damn, it&amp;rsquo;s like finding a secret weapon. Picture this: you need to add fluid animations to your React app but don&amp;rsquo;t want to wrestle with CSS keyframes for hours. Here, 80+ components are ready to copy-paste, with slick effects like border trails and typing text that just work out of the box. Tried the mirror text component—three lines of code and my landing page went from bland to wow. They&amp;rsquo;re open source and free, despite the team logging over 1k dev hours. Perfect for indie devs shipping fast or teams avoiding animation debt. Feels like having a design agency in your node_modules.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Animate UI: Copy-Paste Motion Magic</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/animate-ui/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/animate-ui/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This ain&amp;rsquo;t your grandma&amp;rsquo;s UI library - it&amp;rsquo;s like a component buffet where you grab animated React pieces directly. Tried the cursor follower that dances with your mouse movements, instantly turning dull admin panels into interactive playgrounds. Open-source and free, it plays nice with Shadcn UI like peanut butter and jelly. Toss a fireworks background with typewriter text effects and boom - you&amp;rsquo;ve got a pro landing page in minutes. Perfect for indie devs who want to impress clients without breaking the bank.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>React Bits: Animated Component Library</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/reactbits/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/reactbits/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking into React Bits feels like browsing an animation supermarket—over a hundred components ready to grab, with one-click switching between CSS and Tailwind. I tried the Splash Cursor effect; it sprays water droplets on click, instantly elevating landing pages. Open-source and free with weekly updates, it’s perfect for small teams or solo projects to craft stunning interfaces fast, or even just to borrow animation ideas.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>