<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Social on FindSoFun - Discover Interesting AI Tools &amp; Frontend Libraries</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/social/</link><description>Recent content in Social on FindSoFun - Discover Interesting AI Tools &amp; Frontend Libraries</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:12:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/social/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HiAnime: Instant Anime Stream</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/hianime-4858da/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/hianime-4858da/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Open HiAnime and it feels like walking into a 24/7 anime mart—no sign-up, just click and watch. I tried streaming One Piece and it loaded instantly, with dual audio tracks toggling smoothly. Their mobile app lets you binge on the go, perfect for commutes. The community section buzzes with episode discussions, and you might stumble upon hidden gems. Feels like a daily go-to library for anime lovers, straightforward and reliable.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Digg: Human-First News Community</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/t-c240d4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/t-c240d4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Remember the internet before bot floods and echo chambers? Digg is back with a &amp;lsquo;human-first&amp;rsquo; vibe! Opening this app feels like walking into a party where everyone&amp;rsquo;s actually real—share links, spark discussions, and zero bot interference. I posted about tech news and within minutes got into an AI trend chat with strangers who felt like coffee shop buddies. Niche communities let weirdos thrive, using AI to enhance content but never letting algorithms take over. This renaissance hits different!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>WindowSwap: Global Window Hopping</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/window-swap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/window-swap/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This thing is genius! Click and you&amp;rsquo;re instantly transported to someone&amp;rsquo;s window view in Italy, Japan, or anywhere really. I tried it during a stressful afternoon and found myself calming down watching rain fall through a window in Tellaro. Perfect for virtual travel inspiration, mood setting, or just escaping your own four walls. The authenticity hits different—these are real people&amp;rsquo;s real views, not curated travel footage. Feels like peeking into lives around the world with permission.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>OpenHunts: Product Discovery Playground</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/openhunts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/openhunts/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Walking into OpenHunts feels like entering a tech toy store where new gadgets drop daily. The countdown for Nexty&amp;rsquo;s launch got me hooked instantly. From practical tools like Peerlist internships to mind-blowing AI assistants like Clearo, every discovery feels like unwrapping a present. The voting system is genius - casting 3 daily votes makes you feel like a product judge. Real founder endorsements add authentic credibility. Perfect for competitive research or finding your next dev tool. The community vibe is palpable, like being at a startup demo day every day.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>