<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/data/</link><description>Recent content in Data on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:57:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kaggle YouTube Trending Dataset</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/kaggle-dataset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/kaggle-dataset/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Data Treasure
This is an open dataset collecting global YouTube trending videos data, covering 110 countries and regions with daily updates on video views, likes, comments and other detailed metrics. The dataset includes complete video metadata and channel information, providing a solid foundation for content analysis and trend research.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Efficiency Boost
When you need to analyze trending video patterns from the past six months, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to write your own web crawlers. Simply download this ready-to-use dataset to save significant time and effort. Supports filtering by country and category to quickly identify regional content preferences.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Detailed Design
The data fields are comprehensively designed, recording everything from video publish time and trending dates to channel subscriber counts, even including video resolution and licensed content status. CSV format is well-organized and ready for immediate use.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tech Friendly
The dataset is completely open under CC0 license,可以直接用于机器学习项目和商业分析. The full 9.38GB data package supports bulk download, and works seamlessly with Kaggle&amp;rsquo;s data exploration tools for quick preliminary analysis.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>