<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Webmaster on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/webmaster/</link><description>Recent content in Webmaster on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 11:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/webmaster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PubSpy: Lightning-Fast AdSense Lookup</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/pubspy-adsense-reverse-lookup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/pubspy-adsense-reverse-lookup/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Instant Detection
This tool specializes in AdSense reverse lookup, quickly identifying publisher IDs used by websites. It helps users discover other sites operated by the same publisher, providing a direct solution for finding all ad-monetized sites under one author.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Efficiency Boost
In practical use, simply install the Chrome extension, visit any website and click the icon to immediately get publisher information. Compared to manual queries, speed increases by 50%, with ads.txt detection reduced from 10 seconds to just 5 seconds. Bulk analysis handles hundreds of domains simultaneously, generating comprehensive reports in minutes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>User Experience
The interface is extremely clean, with non-blocking UI showing preliminary results instantly while background processing continues. The extension is only 26KB, loading in under 500ms for smooth operation. All data processing happens locally in the browser, ensuring privacy and security.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Technical Features
Dual API system guarantees 99.99% uptime, while machine learning algorithms predict publisher growth trends. Historical data spans 12 months, with interactive network mapping visualization. Export functionality supports CSV format including traffic data for further analysis.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>SiteData: Privacy-First Website Intelligence</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/sitedata-website-analyzer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/sitedata-website-analyzer/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Traffic Insights
SiteData specializes in website traffic analysis and AdSense reverse lookup, providing quick access to traffic data, keyword rankings, and advertising network information. It simplifies complex website analysis into just a few clicks, making it ideal for digital marketers needing fast competitor intelligence.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Workflow Efficiency
In practical use, it significantly speeds up competitor research - when you see a site with good ad revenue, reverse lookup instantly reveals other sites from the same publisher. For SEO research, you get traffic sources, keyword rankings, and domain data in one place instead of juggling multiple tools.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>User Experience
The interface is clean and intuitive, with dark mode being particularly comfortable for extended data analysis sessions. Functional layout follows logical workflows, and browser extension integration makes the analysis process almost seamless.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Technical Edge
The local processing technology is impressive - all data calculations happen on your device without server transmission. This means you can analyze even sensitive competitor sites without privacy concerns, plus no registration required makes it truly zero-friction to start.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>IDCFlare: Essential Security Tool for Webmasters</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/idcflare-webmaster-tool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/idcflare-webmaster-tool/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Security verification
This is a specialized security verification platform that provides connection security checks for websites. Through simple human verification processes, it ensures visitor authenticity and effectively prevents malicious crawlers and automated attacks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Efficiency boost
For webmasters, deployment significantly enhances website security while reducing server resource waste. Particularly when managing VPS and servers, it filters out substantial invalid traffic, ensuring genuine users enjoy smoother access experiences.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>User experience
The verification interface is clean and intuitive with clearly defined operational steps. Although current page information is limited, the smooth verification process demonstrates well-considered user experience design.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Technical simplicity
The implementation is lightweight and efficient with nearly imperceptible verification procedures. Extremely easy to set up, requiring simple configuration to add security protection, making it ideal for quick deployment on small to medium-sized websites.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>UserJot: All-in-One User Feedback Platform</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/userjot-feedback-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/userjot-feedback-management/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Centralized Collection
UserJot provides a unified platform for gathering and managing user feedback from various sources like Slack, emails, and support tickets. Through an intuitive submission interface, users can easily share ideas while every entry gets systematically tracked. Product teams gain a centralized space to capture all user voices without information fragmentation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Priority Visualization
The tool addresses common pain points where critical bugs get lost in endless threads and low-priority ideas waste engineering resources. Community voting naturally surfaces important requests, clearly showing the difference between features with 10 versus 100 votes. Rich discussion areas provide context behind each request, enabling data-driven product decisions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>User Experience
Designed with usability in mind, the feedback boards feature clean layouts with seamlessly integrated voting and discussion functions. Beautiful changelogs automatically sync with roadmaps, while notification systems alert relevant requesters upon feature releases. Custom domains and branding options maintain consistent product identity across feedback pages.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Technical Simplicity
Setup requires no complicated configuration, allowing immediate feedback collection with free tier including unlimited posts and users. Scalable plans offer enterprise features like advanced search and single sign-on as teams grow. Strong integration capabilities connect with existing workflows, offering low technical barriers with high extensibility.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>ExpiredDomains: Your Go-To for Domain Hunting</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/expireddomains-net-tool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/expireddomains-net-tool/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Domain Goldmine
This platform offers daily updated lists of expired and deleted domains across 677 TLDs, helping users uncover SEO-rich opportunities. It aggregates data from various sources, making it easy to find domains with valuable backlinks or historical significance before they&amp;rsquo;re gone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Efficient Filtering
With advanced filters and sorting options, users can quickly narrow down millions of domains by metrics like backlink count and archive age. This streamlines the hunting process, ideal for both bulk searches and precise finds.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Data-Rich Details
The interface provides comprehensive SEO insights, including TrustFlow, CitationFlow, and Wikipedia links, ensuring informed decisions. Features like watchlists help track desired domains, adding a layer of convenience.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Easy to Use
No technical expertise needed—browse lists or use the fast search to get started. It integrates auctions and buy-now options from platforms like GoDaddy and Sedo, offering a smooth, user-friendly experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>TLD List: Ultimate Domain Comparison Tool</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tld-list-comparison/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/tld-list-comparison/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Domain Discovery
This is a specialized website providing TLD lookup and comparison services, helping users quickly find suitable domain extensions. It compiles global TLD information including pricing, registration requirements, and availability data. Extremely useful for anyone needing to register domains.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Efficient Comparison
In practical use, you can simultaneously compare prices and service terms from multiple domain registrars. Eliminates the hassle of checking each website individually, significantly improving domain registration efficiency. Perfect for bulk registrations or finding the best value domains.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Clean Interface
The website features a minimalist and straightforward design without unnecessary decorations or complex features. Fast loading speeds and clear tabular presentation of results allow users to quickly obtain needed information. This simplicity actually enhances the user experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Technical Execution
Built on web technology, no software installation required. Queries respond quickly with timely data updates, and the operation is intuitive and simple. Even domain registration beginners can easily get started.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>