<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/tags/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on FindSoFun - Discover Cool Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://findsofun.com/en/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>fern: Armchair Documentaries</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-2aa98246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-2aa98246/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Clicking into fern is like opening a living encyclopedia - new discoveries every week. Their documentary topics are brilliantly obscure, from Manhattan&amp;rsquo;s most secret building to fentanyl smuggling routes - all those &amp;lsquo;holy shit they actually made this&amp;rsquo; niche subjects. Watched the CEO kidnapping guide last night, held my breath throughout, more gripping than Netflix series. Perfect for late-night couch sessions with a glass of whiskey to digest these hardcore contents. Their team also runs Simplicissimus channel, double the feast for knowledge hunters.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>JRE: Unfiltered Conversations Hub</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-07f44598/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/youtube-07f44598/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Stepping into Joe Rogan&amp;rsquo;s channel feels like entering a intellectual playground where 3-hour deep dives make you forget about snackable content. Last week he jumped from MMA philosophy to alien civilizations and landed on psychology – that&amp;rsquo;s the magic of unscripted conversations. I often listen while working out, feeling like having a well-read buddy sharing wild stories. The guest lineup alone is worth it: from Elon Musk to underground artists, you never know who&amp;rsquo;s showing up next. It&amp;rsquo;s raw, it&amp;rsquo;s real, and it makes you think deeper about everything.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item><item><title>Digg: Human-First News Community</title><link>https://findsofun.com/en/t-c240d4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://findsofun.com/en/t-c240d4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="product-highlights">Product Highlights&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Remember the internet before bot floods and echo chambers? Digg is back with a &amp;lsquo;human-first&amp;rsquo; vibe! Opening this app feels like walking into a party where everyone&amp;rsquo;s actually real—share links, spark discussions, and zero bot interference. I posted about tech news and within minutes got into an AI trend chat with strangers who felt like coffee shop buddies. Niche communities let weirdos thrive, using AI to enhance content but never letting algorithms take over. This renaissance hits different!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="pricing-model">Pricing Model&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>